<?xml version='1.0' standalone='yes'?>
<bios>
  <bio>
<name> </name>
 	<image>uslogo-500px</image>
  </bio>  
 <bio>
	<name>Laura Ni Dhubhghaill</name>
	<news> I love music videos, podcasts, playing pool, animation, court TV, indie music and dancing. </news>
	<lowdown> I have a B.A. from NUI Maynooth in Media Studies and Greek and Roman Civilization Studies. I worked in a production company for a year making Reality TV shows. I'm not a fan of reality shows myself, you wouldnt believe how much of it is completely constructed. </lowdown>
    <info> I remember playing on a beach on Lake Winnepesauke when I was very tiny. There's a video of that holiday that still exists somewhere, I'd like to see it again. I remember feeling the sand between my toes and the ice creams we all ate together.</info>
	<image>Laura</image>
 </bio>

<bio>
	<name>Melanie Rabier</name>
	<news>French member of the team, globetrotter, 24, and my addiction is chocolate. I love travelling. Airports are one of my favorite places. I grew up in a small touristic city with beautiful long beaches but it was never enough. I needed to go further, discover new cultures, landscapes, way of life, and people in general. However, it is not my only hobby. I love photography. Oh, and I talk too much. </news>
 	<lowdown> Mostly yes. Living in another country and specializing in Multimedia attracted me after a quite original background of study... I never had enough of college, so before coming here I studied: a two years professional degree in Business and Marketing, a Bachelor in Cultural Event Management, a first year Master in Strategy and Communication Management (called Maitrise) and a year in the USA at the University of Oregon (GO DUCKS!). </lowdown>
	<info>I would like to travel. But a more reasonable option is probably to get a job. I will probably fill my backpack and find my way into a new country. I will create new memories! Document them, digitize them and upload them!</info>
	<image>Mel</image>
</bio>
<bio>
	<name>Richard O Connell</name>
	<news> I have many interests! I like music, art, technology, sports and all the spaces in between. But I'm also very flaky and what I like today could easily change tomorrow! :P</news>
  	<lowdown> The dream was always to be either a wrestler or a rockstar but with neither of them coming through in the foreseeable future the new dream is to make digital recall the most successful studio in the world!! :) </lowdown>
	<info> Of course! Technology is changing so fast and how we share our memories is increasingly becoming much more digitalised. When I was young we had  enormous photo albums filled to the brim of stills but now with the ease of the internet social media sites have become the virtual photo album of today's generation. It's great to see it come so far but sad also for the generation that gets left behind.</info>
	<image>Richy</image>

 

</bio>

<bio>
	<name>Cormac O Brien</name>
	<news> Breathing soot under a pre-cooked smiley faced sun in any of Dublin's Parks. I'm a guy with an interest in long division, Joy Division, astrology, cosmology, comic book heroes, comic book losers and everything else outside and in between. The discrete histories of people's lives are unendingly interested to me and I love documentary, film and journalism.</news>
	<lowdown> In a dark room, if you read this please send help.</lowdown>
	<info> No.</info>
	<image>Cormac</image>
</bio>

<bio>     
<name>Austen Donohoe</name>
 	<news> Video production (writing, directing, shooting, editing... I'm in for the long haul!). I'm also rather fond of dreadful films, good films, gaming, all sorts of Metal, and making preparations for the coming zombie apocalypse.</news>
	<lowdown> Aged 4, clearing the first screen of Space Invaders on the Atari 2600. I thought I'd won the game, until the next wave appeared. There's probably a life lesson in there somewhere.</lowdown>
<info> George A. Romero, Chris Morris, Hayao Miyazaki, Bruce Campbell and Sam Raimi, David Simon, Shane Meadows, Lucio Fulci, Quorthon, Larry David, and Tommy Wiseau.</info>
	<image>Austen</image>
</bio>  




</bios>
  